What happened to this city, smoke everywhere. Today
I am telling you about an excellent product related to cancer and heart. If you
like this product, then definitely subscribe to my YouTube channel.
Here you will get 25 lakh cancellation
insurance and Rs. 500000 worth of heart related
problems for just Rs. 3000, Rs. 671 per year.
In an expenditure of Rs. 10 per day, that is,
in a debt of less than one cigarette, you
can get 25 lakh cancer insurance and heart tax of Rs. 5 lakh. The price of your cigarette will
increase in 2-4 years, but the
premium will come from you for 15 years.
Secondly, you will get many more excellent features in this,
but I am telling you an example, here
this is a 35 year old person, he is
taking cancellation insurance of Rs. 40 lakh and insurance of Rs. 20 lakh. If
he gets cancer detector in the early
stage, then he will get 25% of Rs. 40 lakh, that is,
Rs. 10 lakh immediately and the remaining Rs.
30 lakh  The insurance of the policy will continue
but all the premium increases will be
waived but the insurance tax of Rs. 30 lakh is running,
after a few years
how much insurance will be given in case of heart attack,
despite that his cancer insurance tax of Rs. 30 lakh will continue,
okay and this is the tax,
if there is any problem in the minor stage then you
get 25% of the insurance tax together
but if there is a major stage condition
then whatever you have done will be given together,
suppose here if there is a major cancer
then the entire 40 lakh will be given together
or if there is a heart attack then the entire 20 lakh will be given
together, it is not that you will get the
bill that comes on admission in the hospital,
here whatever time you have taken, you get it in
full together, it has nothing to do with any bill in the hospital, along with this
you are getting two more benefits
that whenever there is a minor problem or if there is a
permanent disability in an accident then the
premium payment is automatically waived, along with this
you can see in the next stage
that in minor conditions
You can see here what all taxes are there and in major, whether it is
heart transplant or heart replacement, all these
things you will get here, if it is major then you
get the money all at once, if it is
minor then 25% is given immediately, the rest
of the tax is exempted and the premium is waived,
now I have to google the price of cigarettes also,
so
according to me, a packet
of 10 cigarettes costs 120 rupees, so it
costs more than 10 rupees, 12 rupees, whereas this
insurance is selling for 10 rupees and
secretly, no matter how much people consume
Juba Kesari Mawa Gutkha tobacco in a day,
it is only 3000 rupees, it
is around 3600 rupees with GST, otherwise the
premium is only 3000, it includes 18%
GST, otherwise
in this premium of 1314 plus 1795, you get the entire cancer benefit of 25 lakhs
and heart benefit of 5 lakhs,
if you like the plan then definitely  Purchase it,
contact me on my mobile number 9909403412, thank you, so match